{
    "id": "420168e826024851b4b213592ca193b2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. Rahul, it is a nice film.",
            "description": "According to Rahul means ‘if what Rahul says is true.’",
            "answers": [
                "After",
                "According to",
                "As for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s swim ……………… the river.",
            "description": "We use across to talk about movement in water.",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "over",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………. to refuse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "polite person",
                "too polite person",
                "too polite a person"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She arrived ………………. after breakfast.",
            "description": "Right can mean just or exactly. Rightly means correctly.",
            "answers": [
                "right",
                "rightly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter isn’t here. John isn’t here ………………..",
            "description": "After mentioning a negative idea or fact we can add another negative point by using ‘not…either’.",
            "answers": [
                "also",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that he ………………. told.",
            "description": "Both structures are possible. In American English the structure without ‘should’ is preferred.",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "should be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. having worked hard, she failed the exam.",
            "description": "Before a noun or an ing form we use in spite of. Although and even though are conjunctions used to connect clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "Even though",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m anxious …………….. my brother.",
            "description": "Certain adjectives which describe people’s reactions and feelings are often followed by a to-infinitive. Anxious is one of them.",
            "answers": [
                "contact",
                "to contact",
                "to contacting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………… somebody coming.",
            "description": "To say that we hear something at the moment of speaking we use ‘can hear’. ",
            "answers": [
                "can hear",
                "am hearing",
                "was hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I had hardly closed my eyes …………….. the telephone rang.",
            "description": "Both when and before are possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "than",
                "before",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I had no sooner closed the door .....................… somebody knocked.",
            "description": "Sooner is a comparative form. We use ‘than’ after it.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "when",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner ……………….. to marry him than she started to have terrible doubts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she agree",
                "had she agreed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}